(Howard:)What? No.
(Penny:)Why not?
(Howard:)Because we don't have latent
homosexual feelings toward one another.
(Beverley:)I see.
(Howard:)-No, really. I have a girlfriend now.
-And where is she this evening?
(Howard:)She had to go out of town,
her grandmother died.
(Beverley:)I see.
"Her grandmother died."
Honest to God. Ahem.
Leonard, tell her I have a girlfriend.
(Leonard:)I don't know
what you're talking about.
(Howard:)What do you mean, you don't know
what I'm talking about?
(Howard:)-Tell her I have a girlfriend.
-All right.
He "has" a "girlfriend."
(Howard:)Her name is Bernadette.
She's a waitress, but going to school
to be a microbiologist.
(Beverley:)The more passionately
you stick to this construct...
(Beverley:)...the more you're hurting
your partner.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]